Stop killing babies!
[together] Stop killing babies!
Stop killing babie-
[gasp]
Oh my god, oh my god!
What have I done!?
Don't worry,
...it was empty.
Oh, thank god!
Welcome to heaven, jackass.
What!?
W- W-
What happened?
You got hit by a car
...and died.
[stammers]
Oh my god.
[whimpers]
I-
[stammers]
I'm dead!?
[whimpers]
Uh...
Yeah.
And-
And you're dead too.
Oh!
But you're-
You're just a little baby.
Oh no...
Get the hell off of me!
What're you so upset about?
You people think heaven is this
...grand wonderful place
...and then you spend your whole lives
...desperately trying to avoid getting here.
I, uh- I guess we just
...want a chance to live for a while on Earth.
It's why I'm against abortion.
Everyone has a RIGHT to life.
Why?
So they can sin
...and risk going to hell,
...rather than coming straight to heaven to be happy for eternity?
That's the logical conclusion of the
...heaven-and-hell system.
Best to die early and sinless.
Oh my god!
[sobbing]
So many abortions!
This is
S
SS
SSS
SSSS
SSSSS
SSSSSS
SICK!
Those weren't abortions.
Look at them.
They're way too old.
Now they were already born.
God!?
[gasp]
Glory be thy name!
That's right.
Praise me.
Worship me!
Ooh, oh, oh, yeah.
That's the spot.
Um,
...God?
I- I- I- If-
If those babies
...weren't abortions, then...
...t- t- then what happened to them?
I drowned them.
You...
...drowned them?
These are the flood babies.
The ones who choked to death in water
...when God flooded the world.
THESE are the abortions.
Those
...sick
...bastards!
Hey, careful not to blaspheme.
Right. These were also killed by God in the flood.
God drowned plenty of pregnant women too, remember?
Oh.
O- O-
I- I'm sorry,
...God.
I- I- I-
I didn't know.
That's right.
You apologized to me
...for not wanting me to terminate those pregnancies.
Oh okay.
I'm- I'm sorry.
But...
...where are the actual abortions
...done by actual people?
Oh.
Those start over here.
Those
...sick
...bastards!
Well, there you go blaspheming again.
But- But-
But you said
...these abortions were done by people.
On orders
...from God.
What!?
No, no,
...God would never order an abortion.
Uh- Uh- God said,
"Before I formed you in the womb,"
"...I knew you,"
"...and before you were born"
"...I consecrated you;"
"I have appointed you"
"...as a prophet"
"...to the nations."
Jeremiah,
...chapter 1, verse 5.
Hey,
...genius.
Was I addressing you
...or Jeremiah?
Um...
Jeremiah?
So do you think it applies to you?
Or are you also 'a prophet to the nations' too?
Um,
...no.
But...
...don't you have a plan
...for everyone you form in the womb?
God doesn't really form anyone in the womb.
Um, that's an entirely observable natural process.
Yeah, what do you think my 'plan' was
...for all those dead babies you just saw?
Did I 'form them in the womb'
...just to live a short meaningless life on Earth
...only to be choked to death on water and a flood?
Um...
I don't know.
Did you?
Hell yeah, I did!
Up high!
[demonic voice] I SAID UP HIGH!
Uh-huh.
What's wrong. Jeffrey?
You're looking...
...awfully pale.
It's just all this talk about baby-killing and-
Hey.
It's-
It's God.
I- I- I-
I don't know his reasons
...for ending a baby's life
...o- o- or ending a pregnancy,
...but I have faith in his reasons b-
...because,
...well,
...h- he's God!
You don't need to have faith in his reasons
...because his reasons
...are clearly explained in the Bible.
God is pro-abortion.
What!?
God is NOT pro-abortion.
Um...
Hell yeah, I am.
What!?
But-
But I thought-
Let me ask you something:
Do you think a woman
...should have an abortion
...if she gets pregnant by cheating on her husband?
No.
No, of course not.
It's not the baby's fault she cheated.
That baby still has a right to life.
Nope!
I commanded that they be aborted.
I think my wife
...hath cheated on me.
I suspects I'm not the one who got her pregnant.
Bring forth the magic abortion potion.
If she drinks this magic abortion potion
...and nothing happens,
...then she did not cheat.
BUT
...if she drinks this magic abortion potion
...and she did cheat,
...then she will have a miscarriage.
So be it.
Bottoms up!
You...
...are NOT the father.
[cheers and applause in the backrgound]
I told you! I told you! I-
See?
Makes sense, doesn't it?
Well...
You wouldn't want to be a
...CUCK,
...would ya?
No!
Well then.
Makes sense,
...doesn't it?
Y- Yeah.
Yeah, it does.
And this
...was the fetus
...that she miscarried.
Your mother was a WHORE!
A WHORE!
[laughs]
Hell yeah, she was.
Up high!
Okay, you guys are really starting to scare me.
Oh, relax.
You're not a fetus
...o- o- or part of a large group.
I'm sure God
...would not target a specific infant.
Oh, wouldn't I?
I punished David by killing his child.
Not only that,
...but I made that little son of a bitch
...suffer for seven days
...before he finally died.
In other words,
...God performed a seven-day-long
...post-birth abortion.
In this case,
...the purpose of David's child's life,
...the reason he was
...'formed in the womb', as you say,
...was literally to suffer and die
...in order to torment his father.
Well...
I mean...
Maybe his father
...should not have shown contempt for the Lord.
Now that's what I'm talking about!
Wait.
So you agree?
I- I-
I don't know.
Maybe.
In Joshua, chapter 7,
...verses 24 through 36,
...God had Achan's children
...stoned and burned
...because Achan stole some loot.
God would not allow Israel to win a battle
...until those children were killed.
God literally made it
...so they weren't allowed to kill other people
...until they killed some children first.
Well...
I mean, their dad did steal
...and those kids
...probably knew he stole, so...
My man!
But they were just children!
In Numbers, chapter 16, verses 27 through 33,
...God opens up the earth
...and swallows children and babies
WHOLE
...just to prove to everyone
...that he was the one who sent Moses.
Because they were questioning his authority.
Oh. W-
Well, if they were questioning Moses' authority,
...then shouldn't the earth
...swallow their babies whole?
Obviously!
You come from a country
...that was BUILT upon questioning authority,
...not blindly giving into it.
Do you honestly think
...not blindly following a country's leader
...means your children should be brutally killed?
Well...
In Hosea, chapter 9,
...verses 12 through 14, it says,
"Even if they rear children,"
"...I will bereave them of everyone."
"The Lord will give them WOMBS"
"...that MISCARRY."
Abortions.
Why?
For the crime of worshiping other gods.
You sided with this god
...from the comfort of an advanced First World country
...that allows the freedom
...to worship any god.
So do you honestly think
...people who belong to other religions
...should be forced to have abortions?
Should these forced abortions
...become the law of the land in America?
Well, it's in the Bible,
...so...
...I guess.
Maybe.
Besides,
...God did it,
...so it wasn't the same as
...people giving other people abortions.
On the contrary,
...had you been born back then,
...you could have been commanded to do it.
Could you have gone through with it?
In 1 Samuel, chapter 15, verse 3,
...God explicitly requires soldiers
...to kill children and infants.
"Do not spare them," it says.
"Put them to the death."
And in Numbers,
...chapter 31, verse 17,
...he demands the DEATHS
...of all the male children
...and non-virgin women,
...which included pregnant women.
How about that, Mister Pro-life?
Would you kill a pregnant woman
...or a child
...if God told you to do it?
Well...
If God says to do it,
...then it isn't wrong.
Exactly.
You know, I'm really starting to like you.
Thanks, God!
But literally anybody
...can claim to do something in the name of God.
PEOPLE wrote the Bible,
...not God.
How can you tell the difference between the justifications
...of someone who personally wants to kill
...thousands of children
...versus someone who SAYS
...that 'God told them'
...to kill thousands of children?
Well, I- I- I-
I guess I would just try to figure out
...which one is the sane person
...who wants to kill thousands of children.
Easy peasy,
...lemon squeezy!
Look.
When you lend THIS much authority to the Bible
...you are not being anti-abortion,
...you are setting up a way
...for someone who claims to know the mind of God
...to have the ultimate say on who should be aborted
...and who should be killed,
...who should have rights
...and who should have none.
That could be
...literally anybody.
Wait.
Who says I'm anti-abortion anymore?
Um...
But you just died
...while protesting an abortion clinic.
That's before I knew
...God used it so much to punish people.
Not even you
...could justify the punishment for riling God's jealousy.
In Hosea, chapter 13, verse 16,
...which says,
"Their little ones will be dashed to the ground."
"...their pregnant women"
"...ripped open."
What?
I was jealous.
Yeah, they knew God is a jealous god.
Exactly.
So w-
...why shouldn't they rip open pregnant women
...an- and dash infants to the ground?
A perfectly logical reaction.
Isaiah, chapter 13, verse 16,
"Their infants will be dashed to pieces before their eyes;"
"...their houses will be looted"
"...and their wives violated."
That's right.
Dash those wives to pieces
...and violate those infants!
Uh, uh...
N- No, it's-
It's the other way.
I- I mean, vi- viola-
Right, right. Violate-
[together] ...those wives and dash those infants.
Violate wives, dash infants.
Got it.
Nahum, chapter 3, verse 10,
...to the city God declared himself to be against,
...their, quote,
"Infants were dashed to pieces"
"...at every corner."
I'm detecting a pattern.
Lots of infant dashing.
Yeah, I do tend to favor
...infant dashing, don't I?
In Deuteronomy, chapter 28, verse 18,
...for disobedience it says, quote,
"I will curse the FRUIT of your WOMB."
And remember, that's
...someone who wrote that on God's behalf,
...a mere mortal
...calling the unborn 'cursed'.
You believing God said it,
...and then the rest of that entire chapter
...is about how God will have people tormented
...to the point of EATING
...their own CHILDREN
...just for not appreciating him enough.
Fine, then.
It's God!
Eat the babies!
Dash the babies to pieces!
Drown the babies!
Kill the babies!
If it's in the Bible,
...it's in the Bible!
Who am I to argue?
Damn, you are awesome!
Kill the babies!
[laughs]
You know what?
I haven't done this since J.C.,
...but you deserve a second chance at life, my man.
[laughs]
Terminate pregnancies!
More abortion!
So I'm sending you back.
Kill.
Pregnant.
Women!
[laughs]
Enjoy your time back on Earth, my man!
Kill babies!
Kill the babies!
Well.
That didn't take long.
A baby!
Oh, shit.
Get him!
Oh hey, Joseph.
What's up?
My Lord.
My wife, Mary,
...is with child,
...and I have not knocked her up.
I suspect her
...of cheating on me
...with Chad.
Ah, n-
No, no, no, that's okay.
I'm-
I'm pretty sure it's cool.
But, my Lord,
...I wish for her to drink the customary
...magic potion
...that will give her an abortion
...if she cheated on me.
Okay.
Hang on.
One second.
Here, keep this on.
Magic abortion potion is incoming.
Er- Oh, okay.
Uh, drink up.
She should be fine.
No cheating.
No cheating whatsoever.
Hey guys, we got a problem.
What now?
It's the new video we just uploaded.
What could possibly go wrong with it?
I had my social media guy DarkMatter handling.
That guy's a genius.
The video is fine,
...it's the comments.
Let me guess.
Yep.
[together] "That was the Old Testament!"
"We are following New Testament!"
Do they think that God of the Old Testament
...is not the same as the God of the New Testament or something?
I don't think so.
So what's the problem then?
I'm still the same guy.
They think the Old Testament standards don't apply to them,
...except for the ones they like.
What!?
Why?
Because ever since J.C. came along,
...they get to cherry-pick.
Oh.
So they're cool with
...SOME people getting different rules than others.
Yeah, it seems that way.
And they don't even think that
...some of my rules and actions,
...even if they're just in the Old Testament,
...can give clues as to my nature as a deity,
...which could then be used to judge
...whether or not I'm even real
...and/or worthy of worship?
Correctamundo!
Well, it seems they must have
...pretty high standards then.
High standards?
It seems they don't have any.
On the contrary, Jeffery,
...they have
...DOUBLE the standards.
Ha!
[chuckles]
Good one, God.
What?
I-
I made a joke?
I don't-
I don't get it.